

# Tom Axblad

Ø 073-9444934
⋈ tom.axblad@gmail.com

#### About me

With a great affinity for graphics and games since I was a child, I have always had an interest in learning programming and development since I first encountered programming as a concept. This has led me to specialising within Visualisations and Graphics to learn more creative applications of programming, resulting in my degree job suggesting a foveated rendering technique using eye tracking in VR.

## Experience

#### 2018-2020 **Teacher Assistant**, KTH, Stockholm.

As a teacher's assistant I helped students understand the material and solve difficult problems. Working as an assistant gave me a deeper knowledge about how to communicate effectively with different types of people, as well as how to understand what is missing in order for a person to understand complex concepts.

### 2018-2019 IT Responsible, MiToo, Stockholm.

As responsible for everything IT, I both provided other employees with data and custom programs to facilitate their work, and was responsible for the migration of the old e-commerce system to the new system.

## 2013-2014 Support Agent, Vaimo, Stockholm.

Provided support for customers via Zendesk's mail service as well as through the phone, and was responsible for handling all personal contact and needs for the premium customers of the company. I also improved and worked on the web design of said companies.

#### Education

# 2018–2020 Masters Programme - Computer Science: Visualisation and Graphics, KTH, Stockholm

The Visualisation and Graphics specialisation within the Computer Science Master focused on how to apply advanced algorithms and Mathematics in order to create impressive and informative visualisations, renderings and interactive applications. Complementing the specialisation with parallel programming has given me the knowledge on how to use multi threaded hardware for fast rendering, problem solving, and other applications.

# 2015–2020 **Degree Programme - Computer Science and Engineering**, *KTH*, Stockholm. 5-year education that provides good knowledge in programming, advanced mathematics, entrepreneurship, and working in major projects.

2013 **Military Education, Telecom warfare track, LedR**, *Försvarsmakten*, Enköping. An education that lasted for three months. Worked a lot in a group of group assignments. Taught me to quickly handle and carry out difficult tasks that I have no previous experience with. The education included risk management, group collaboration, law, physical activities, mental endurance, physical endurance and isolated solving of very difficult tasks.

Teacher's Assistant: Courses

2020 Master course: Introduction to Visualization

Lab Assistant, Exercise Responsible, Examiner

2019-2020 Basic Programming

Lab Assistant

Programming Languages

 $\begin{array}{c} \mathsf{C} & & \mathsf{C} + + \\ \mathsf{Java} & & \mathsf{Rust} \end{array}$ 

C# Javascript
HTML CSS
XML Python

Has experience with Unity, Blender, Photoshop, and Premiere Pro

References

Given out upon request.